<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on oct.zoy.org</title>
    <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on oct.zoy.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; oct.zoy.org, questions, comments, critics [@octplane](https://twitter.com/octplane)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oct.zoy.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🚘 Remote: my setup</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2022-06-29-remote-1-my-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2022-06-29-remote-1-my-setup/</guid>
      <description>Just like The Setup, but more amateur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🏢 Hiring at Datadog</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2022-06-26-hiring-at-datadog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2022-06-26-hiring-at-datadog/</guid>
      <description>Hiring is tough. This article describes my interviewer&amp;rsquo;s experience at Datadog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚮 The Ad Blocking Problem</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/the-ad-blocking-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/the-ad-blocking-problem/</guid>
      <description>How I&amp;rsquo;m currently blocking Ads at home, and why? In this article, I&amp;rsquo;m writing about the various solutions I&amp;rsquo;ve recently explored to block ads and I also describe the solution I&amp;rsquo;m currently using!
Pi-hole Pi-hole is a cool open source project to block ads on your whole network. You set this up on a small Raspberry Pi (hence the name, heh), and then reconfigure your internet to use the pi-hole as your primary DNS, it will then nuke carefully all DNS requests sent to this tracking and ads endpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚨 Git GPG and notifications</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/git-gpg-and-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/git-gpg-and-notifications/</guid>
      <description>This article is pretty old, so be careful as its information could be out of date!
 this article is for macOS only.
If you use git and gpg to sign your commits, then you&amp;rsquo;re probably used to sign you commits using a physical key that you have to insert and press with your finger when you are creating a commit.
Unfortunately, there is no visible feedback in the console when git awaits for a yubikey touch and this means that you can sometime miss these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4️⃣ four links</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-12-28-4-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-12-28-4-links/</guid>
      <description>4 noteworthy links from this week:  Let your code type-hint itself: introducing open source MonkeyType: an excellent occasion to revisit type hinting in Python cats 1.0.0: for Scala-f-ists! Why TLS 1.3 isn&amp;rsquo;t in browsers yet: a big in-depth article about TLS Questions about Chatbots: a nice overview of this technology that is supposed to change the world ;)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎯 Ansible Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-02-27-ansible-tips-and-tricks-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-02-27-ansible-tips-and-tricks-2/</guid>
      <description>If you have been doing a bit of Ansible, there is probably some coding style that has emerged from your work, especially if you work in a team around the same code. During my time as an Ansible developer, I had the opportunity to collect some tips I use on a regular basis when writing scripts. These tips will probably help you save some time.
I assume that you already know Ansible, Playbooks, YAML syntax and Ansible Galaxy roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5️⃣ five short links</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-04-21-five-short-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-04-21-five-short-links/</guid>
      <description>Tech  remote attack on an ODB dongle, follow-up of last week links: It was obvious this will lead to some dirty exploitation. on Recursion, Continuations and Trampolines, an excellent in-depth article that speaks about tail call optimization and all these way to avoid exhausting the stack. how r/places  was built for reddit 1st of April event. Technical and inspiring. Real life challenges :)  Culture  a simple RPG rule system you can use anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6️⃣ six short links</title>
      <link>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-04-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oct.zoy.org/posts/2017-04-14/</guid>
      <description>Tech  Ellie is a nice webapp that allows prototyping of Elm-lang based applications. Elm is a javascript alternative, looks a lot like Haskell. Track your vehicle using using a ODB dongle, nice way to have a connected car. an iOS alternative that can probably do the job at last for some prototyping, or connected self: SensorLog by Bernd Thomas. I just need a PaaS to store the data and render them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
